Guide to the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Papers TAM.694
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV. Rabbi of Congregation B'nai Jacob and Park East Synagogue Records, 1942-2016, undated; 1965-2016; 2 audiocassettes; 6 film reels; 8.45 Gigabytes in 1,975 computer files.; 25 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 49 manuscript boxes, 5 half manuscript boxes, 1 small flat box, 2 oversize flat b
  - Booklet -- The American Study Center for Peace and Interfaith Dialogue Mt. Zion, Jerusalem, Israel, undated; 1 folder (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Booklet and Photograph -- The White House, undated; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 21)
  - Brochure -- Presidential Luncheon Committee, undated; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence -- Center of Israel Studies, the Chinese Institute for Peace and Development Studies, undated; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Dinner Invitation to the Permanent Mission of China to the United Nations, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence -- Invitation to the Celebration of 50th Anniversary of the Salvation of Bulgarian Jews, undated; 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence -- Qatar Foundation for Education, Science and Community Development, undated; 1 folder (Box 262, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence -- Visits to China, undated; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - Documents, undated; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Design Plan -- The Center for Jewish Studies at Nanjing University, undated; 1 folder (Box 235, Folder 13)
  - Film and Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Films, undated (Box 197, Film 694.0021, 694.0022, Box 204, Film 694.0052)
  - Image, undated; 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Images, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_50
  - Images -- Holbrooke, Ambassador Richard at PES, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_21
  - Images -- Political and Religious Leaders, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_17
  - Images -- Powell, Colin and Orthodox Christian and Catholic Leaders, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_16
  - Images and Video Recordings -- Visits to Korea, France, and Japan, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_10
  - Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Negatives -- Beijing, China, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Negatives -- Conference in London, England, undated; 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Negatives -- Shanghai and Nanjing, China, undated; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - Notes -- Uganda, undated; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 15)
  - Photograph -- Elsenstadt, Michael, Joyce Hearst, Elizabeth Schneier, Ken Auletta, and Rabbi Arthur Schneier, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - Photograph -- Rosen, Chief Rabbi at Iasi, Romania, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, undated; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur and Elizabeth Schneier at PES, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur at Israeli Ambassador Yaacobi's Residence in 1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur at Warsaw Ghetto Memorial with Chief Rabbi Rosen, undated; 1 folder (Box 242, Folder 16)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Archbishop Sambi in Washington, D.C., undated; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 21)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Cuban President Fidel Castro, 1994; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Ehud Olmert, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with President George W. Bush and John Negroponte, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Photograph -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Professor Xu Xin, undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, undated
    - Digital Images, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_20; 5 folders
    - Paper Files (Box 125, Folder 3, 23, Box 213, Folder 16, Box 243, Folder 12, Box 251, Folder 9)
  - Photographs -- Arens at PES in 1989, undated; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Photographs -- From the Foreign Affairs Bureau of the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, undated; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Photographs -- Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Photographs -- Jewish Theological Seminary in Budapest with Russian Students, undated; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur at the Russian Embassy, undated; 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur at Various AAD, undated; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur at Various Events, undated; 2 folders (Box 125, Folder 27, Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Chinghiz Aitmatov at New York and Washington, D.C., undated; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Dalai Lama, undated; 1 folder (Box 239, Folder 13)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Elizabeth Schneier, undated; 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Elizabeth Schneier and the Archbishop of Canterbury, 1990s, undated; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Elizabeth Schneier and President Bill Clinton in New York City, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Madeleine Albright at Abe Foxman's Book Party, undated; 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Myron Minskoff, undated; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Pope Benedict XVI and at the UN, undated; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 21)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with President Ceaucescu in 1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Religious and Government Leaders, undated; 1 folder (Box 280, Folder 16)
  - Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Soviet Students, undated; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Photographs -- Various Events, undated; 2 folders (Box 150, Folder 13, 19)
  - Photographs and Images -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with President Menem of Argentina and Politicians, undated; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Photographs and Press -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Czech Republic Secretariat for Religious Affairs Vladimir Janku, undated; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Poster -- Brotherhood of Man Sculpture, undated; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Press -- Dr. Arthur Schneier Appointed First Director of International Affairs Institute at Yeshiva University, undated; 1 folder (Box 261, Folder 14)
  - Press, undated; 2 folders (Box 214, Folder 1, 2)
  - Program Drafts -- 2005 Dialogue Between Cultures and Civilizations, undated; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Sound Recording -- A Memorial Tribute to the Honorable Yitzchak (Ijo) Bager, undated (Box 197, Cassette 694.0003)
  - Speech -- PES Dinner, undated; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 24)
  - Transcript -- National Radio Pulpit NBC Radio, undated; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Video Recording -- Jewish and Chinese Relations, undated; TW_TAM_694_ER_82